One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
That's why we gotta cast off - together, we can!
Sailing from sea to sea,
saying it's nothing but a fairy tale.
Truth is stranger than fiction, isn't it?
Don't pretend you can't see it.
Common sense is only what the majority says it is!
It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
So let's go, Captain I'll-Do-It-My-Way!
Whaddya mean, "no can do"?
We haven't even started yet!
I wanna know it all! Now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can! This moment...
We can! I can! With this feeling of freedom...
Now... Now, oh yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
Duke Inuarashi and Master Nekomamushi
A mammoth?!
Why's that prehistoric animal here?!
So that's what your enemies wanted, and what you people didn't have?
A warrior from the Land of Wano? Raizo?
We don't know such a person!
D-Don't mess with this country! Get out!
So it was real!
The unknown country of the Mink Tribe!
You silly animals talk a lot!
Identify yourselves!
Who are you-gara people?!
Hmm?
Who do you think you're asking to identify themselves?!
This man right here is...
...the infamous Emperor Kaido-sama's right-hand man!
One of the three henchmen who are called "Disasters"!
Prominent member of the Beasts Pirates
Captain of the Mammoth
Jack the Drought
Jack the Drought-sama!
The land that he passed through...
...will be destroyed -
ruined as if a drought occurred.
Now, hand over Raizo,
the warrior from the Land of Wano, to us!
You don't want your quiet life
Beasts Pirates
Headliner of the Gifters
Sheepshead
in which you can hold your kid to be threatened!
Or do you wanna fight?! Huh?!
We definitely don't want to fight.
Mon-ji!
However, we need you to listen to us in order to come to an agreement.
We can't hand over someone who isn't here.
Jack-san, we Minks don't lie.
If you want to look for this Raizo,
you can go from door to door...
He has no mercy even for women, children, or elderly people!
Are we here to talk, Ginrummy?
No, Jack-sama.
We're here to capture a samurai.
Raizo is not a samurai, you idiot!
He's a ninja!
Cut it out, Sheepshead-sama!
Samurai is a general term for all kinds of warriors from the Land of Wano! Either way is okay!
Samurai and ninja aren't the same!
I only have one demand!
Bring Raizo here!
So it was Kaido's subordinates who attacked this country.
That's right.
We don't know anyone named Raizo!
Stop asking for the impossible!
We really don't know!
Then, search the length and breadth of the country!
Pleasures!
My boy!
Silly kid! Show them how merciless we can be!
Pleasures
Ouch!
What are you guys doing?
What's with them?!
How pathetic they are!
We have no weaklings in this country!
All of us Minks are born to be gifted fighters!
Even a baby knows how to defend itself!
You-gara people, do you think you can fight all the people in this country?
We even have highly-trained Musketeers whose abilities are beyond words!
If we fight, both of our troops will get hurt!
If you want to look for someone, could you at least have a talk with the duke of our country?
A talk?
I refuse!
Gifters! Come forward!
Okay!
Gifters
What's with their-gara bodies?!
Alright! Destroy the country and find the samurai!
They didn't listen to us at all and the fight began.
The peaceful Kurau City was...
...instantly turned into a battlefield!
Those who could walk helped those who couldn't
and carried them here.
We don't know how they-teia got to this island
or what made them think that the samurai was here.
I bet the mammoth was so big!
Don't get excited!
Now isn't the time for that!
By listening to Wanda-san's story,
you know why I said "samurai" and "Land of Wano" are taboo now, don't you?
You're right.
What bad people!
So if you use those words, you'll anger them and make them hate you.
So, anyway...
The ninja that Kin'emon was talking about isn't here!
What a letdown!
Ninja?
Bone-Bone Chop!
Chop! Chop! Chop!
By "ninja," you mean a warrior from the Land of Wano?
You-teia, do you know something?
No, no, he definitely didn't say such a thing!
Oh, "kanja"!
He was asking how the patient is doing!
Note: kanja = patient
Garchu!
It doesn't hurt at all...
And are we almost there at the patient's house?
Yes, I see Duke-sama's sanatorium already.
Thank you for coming with me.
I'll tell you the rest of the story later.
Duke Inuarashi's Sanatorium
We're sorry, Shishilian-sama!
Please forgive us!
Shishilian-sama is raging out of control!
What's going on?
Shishilian-dono! What's the matter?!
Oh, Wanda!
They-gara kept saying sweet things...
...so I just pushed them off the cliff!
Captain of Duke Inuarashi's Musketeers (Lion Mink)
Full Power Shishilian
Generosity!
Love!
Romance!
Babies!
Sugar!
Honey!
Don't ever talk about sweet stuff
in my presence!
Or I'll bite out your windpipe!
Now, climb up here without help!
He's so generous!
What did you just say?!
What?!
How could you talk about such sappy stuff like love or generosity so soon after I told you not to!?
But still, he's cool...
We're sorry!
We'll never say anything sweet again!
All right then!
Shishilian-dono.
What?!
They-teia are the Straw Hats.
Thank you for saving my country!
I'll be indebted to you forever!
Shishilian-dono puts all his power into everything.
What an annoying lion.
The duke is expecting you!
You can go in! Hurry up!
Luffy and everybody!
Mokomo Dukedom Day Ruler Duke Inuarashi
Duke-sama! I'm glad that you're okay!
So you-gara people are the Straw Hats?
You saved us in every way.
Thank you very much.
I heard my crew saved your people but I haven't gotten to hear the whole story yet.
Well, you-gara and the rest saved us too, Straw Hat Luffy-kun.
Anyway, I bet you're strong!
I mean, really strong!
What?! That's rude!
Duke-sama is the mightiest warrior in the country!
Hey, stop.
That's not what you call a loser.
You're not a loser!
The enemies were surely troublesome but we had the upper hand!
It was...
...a poison-gas weapon.
Gas?
That's right, Luffy.
This country was ruined by Caesar's poison-gas weapon!
Caesar created the weapon and Doflamingo trafficked it and it made it all the way to Kaido!
Caesar!
He's drooling!
I know how you feel! He-teia saved us too!
What a delicious-looking savior.
You're not fully recovered yet so...
not now.
Not now or ever!
Well, let's not talk about the loss.
You-gara, that straw hat looks quite good on you.
I was once...
Oh, I can't remember who it was!
That cat...
Master Nekomamushi.
I was once traveling across the seas with that one.
Shanks who is one of the Four Emperors now was wearing that kind of hat then.
What?!
Old man, do you know Shanks?! How?!
I got this hat from him and...
He fell asleep!
It's already six o'clock.
It's only six! He's not a kid!
Hey, wake up!
Like I mentioned earlier, the Mokomo Dukedom is governed by two rulers all the time.
Duke Inuarashi is the official ruler but...
Master Nekomamushi who guards the old sacred Whale Forest possesses the same right.
What does it have to do with him falling asleep?!
I said "Stop"!
They really don't like each other.
When they come face to face,
they might try to kill one another.
Kill one another?!
Why?!
I don't know why.
I heard they used to be best friends.
But they're both well-respected kings, even if they fight, it'll be an equal match.
They had too many fights and they don't even wanna face each other now...
So one of them, from six in the morning
to six in the evening with the sun
and another from six in the evening
to six in the morning with the moon.
That's how they split their living hours.
They hate each other that much?
I didn't realize the doctors were sleeping too!
All of the people in this fortress should be sleeping now.
I'm getting tired. Grr...
You are...
Shishilian! Always at full power!
You don't have to yell! I hear you!
The day-and-night shifts are affecting us too.
The people of the city are active during the day.
And the people of the forest...
...are nocturnal...
Find him!
I know Raizo is in this country!
Stop!
Don't destroy the city anymore!
If nothing is done...
Where's the samurai?!
I don't know! I really don't know!
Then, go to hell.
Here come the Musketeers!
Great! Let them-gara handle it!
Everyone else, just step back!
Minimize damage!
The Musketeers
Try to disarm them!
Yes!
Let's go!
Okay!
What's wrong with them-teia?
So creepy!
There are some odd warriors here.
Is that a race we don't know?!
They-teia have strange abilities!
Watch out for those with black horns!
Wolf Grip!
His hand turned into a wolf!
Go to hell!
Wanda!
You-gara, step back!
Shishilian-dono!
The Three Inuarashi Musketeers
The Three Musketeers!
All available Musketeers,
lead the citizens to the forest!
Yes!
Who are they?!
Duke Inuarashi!
You're Jack, aren't you?
Stop this vandalization and violence now!
You must be the ruler of this country!
What?!
Duke-sama!
Why did you drop your sword?!
We're not gonna resist!
You can search the country or the island...
...for that samurai, all you want!
So stop the destruction!
This country has a glorious history!
I refuse!
Duke-sama, run!
Duke-sama!
Whoa-whoa! What's with that dog?!
He withstood Jack-sama's attack!
That's our Duke Inuarashi!
I didn't know they had such a strong guy!
I thought this was a fairyland of fuzzy animals!
Screw you!
Our boss, Jack-sama is a great pirate renowned throughout the New World!
The bounty on his head is...
...one billion belly!
So just because you're a little strong,
don't think you can push your luck!
This underling sure is obnoxious.
Please!
It's a false accusation!
We're not hiding the samurai!
Let me make it clear!
We'll call off our attack as soon as we get the samurai!
If you don't have him, it's your own fault!
That doesn't make any sense.
Let me tell you one more thing.
I like destroying stuff.
This is certainly a disaster!
Kill them all!
Let's go!
What an unbelievable amount of rainfall!
Don't be intimidated by such rain!
That's Master Nekomamushi's roar!
The Fool of the Night woke up!
Let's retreat, Musketeers!
What?!
Aren't we gonna fight with them?
No, the day-and-night shifts are working.
We can stay on the offensive without giving them a break.
You're right!
Jack!
Don't think you-gara are the only unreasonable man here!
Anywhere you go, you can find a fool!
Amulet: protect
It's my country when the moon is up!
I won't let any invaders get away!
The Guardians
Don't think you can get out of here alive!
It's giant!
A cat monster!
Jack-sama!
Master, the city is...
Never mind! I heard what's going on.
You came looking for a warrior from the Land of Wano, didn't you?
I wouldn't let any samurai step onto the island!
If they come in,
I'd be the first to bite them to death!
I'm Nekomamushi!
The man who waits for the dawn of the world!
Warden of the Whale Forest
Night Ruler
Master Nakomamushi
Jack-sama!